Effective as of July 6, 2026

Privacy Policy
--------------

([View previous version](https://www.grammarly.com/privacy-policy-march-2025))

Welcome to Superhuman. A little bit about us: We’re the productivity platform that brings AI to you everywhere you work, however you work. When you use Superhuman products, you’re trusting us to handle your personal data with care. We take that trust seriously. We make money when users purchase our paid products and not by selling or monetizing user content. We offer a free product and hope you’ll purchase one of our paid products. 

This Privacy Policy describes how Superhuman Platform Inc. (formerly Grammarly) and our subsidiaries (such as Grammarly Inc., Coda Project LLC, and Superhuman Labs LLC) and affiliated companies (collectively, “Superhuman”, “we,” or “us”), collect, use, and disclose information about you, as well as privacy choices available to you. We offer lots of tools to different people and organizations, so we need to explain when this Privacy Policy applies:

*   This Privacy Policy applies when you interact with us as an individual, such as when you create an account, receive our products directly from us, or browse our websites. 
    
*   Unless we tell you a different policy applies, this Privacy Policy covers our products, including those offered as “Grammarly”, “Docs” (formerly known as “Coda”), “Superhuman Go”, and “Superhuman Mail”. It also covers your interactions with and on our online marketplace (if you build, access, use, purchase, or integrate third-party products in our marketplace, additional terms will apply).  
    
*   If you use our products under the management of a company, organization, educational institution, or other legal entity (such as if your employer gives you access to our inbox assistant tools for work or if you open an account on behalf of an entity), this Privacy Policy won’t apply to the information you upload to or output from our products.  Please see more info [below](https://superhuman.com/legal/privacy-policy#sectionSingleColumn_3dPvw48Jj6feFVRw9O1UMj). 

Below, we provide some additional privacy information for those living in the [United States](https://superhuman.com/legal/privacy-policy#sectionSingleColumn_5NmYRVyPVFaYtmVFLBd6Nu) (US), the [European Union, the European Economic Area (EEA), the United Kingdom (UK), or Switzerland](https://superhuman.com/legal/privacy-policy#sectionSingleColumn_11U1b02vomi138QlYdrrAr).

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time by publishing an updated version. If we make material changes, we will provide you additional notice, such as by sending you an email.

Contents
--------

Information We Collect
----------------------

The information we collect depends on how you use our products and how you manage your privacy settings.

We collect information you provide to us. This includes:

*   Account information: When you create an individual or organizational account, we collect information such as your email address, password, name, email preferences, job titles, and phone numbers. If you use a single sign-on partner, like Google or Apple, we’ll collect the information from them that you authorize.
    
*   Payment information: If you make a purchase or payment with us, we collect information about the transaction, and our third-party payment processor will handle your payment information. 
    
*   User content: We receive the content you upload or enable our products to access, such as emails and drafts, text, screen content, web pages, documents, files, calendars, images, data, and any other content you allow our products to access. 
    
*   Voice data: If you choose to use our Notetaker or transcription features, we collect recordings to create transcriptions of communications captured through our services, including recordings of other participants.
    
*   Communications with us and feedback: You may have the option to submit additional information to us as you use our products or when you interact with our customer support or sales teams. For example, you may choose to participate in surveys where you can provide feedback about our products. 

We collect some information automatically. We do this when you use our products or browse our websites, for example. This includes: 

*   Technical information: We collect technical information about your device and how you access our products. This includes your IP address, device type, browser type and version, apps installed on your device, time zone setting and location, browser plugin types and versions, operating system, and platform. Depending on how you use our products, we may also collect technical information about third-party apps and tools where you use our products.
    
*   Usage data: We collect usage data about how you interact with us and our products, including your activity on our websites and apps and your interactions with our marketing communications. We collect usage data about actions you take using our products, such as logs of which features you use and data from these features, like read receipts, security logs, as well as quality and performance information about the operation of our products. We also collect data about how you interact with our online marketplace, such as if you access, use, develop, or purchase an offering on the marketplace or integrate third-party marketplace products into your Superhuman account(s). 
    
*   Cookie information: We use cookies and similar technologies, such as pixels and local storage technology, (collectively, “Cookies”) to collect some of the technical information and usage data described above, including to recognize your browser or device. Below, we describe how we use Cookies for advertising and the [choices you have](https://superhuman.com/legal/privacy-policy#sectionSingleColumn_1oJ1lf5uPObRHb9hkmKhRa), and we also provide more information about Cookies in the [Additional European Information](https://superhuman.com/legal/privacy-policy#sectionSingleColumn_11U1b02vomi138QlYdrrAr) section and in the [Privacy and Data Rights, Choices and Cookies page](https://support.grammarly.com/hc/en-us/articles/40540355410957-Superhuman-Privacy-and-Data-Rights-Choices-and-Cookies). 

Information about non-users. Your user content may include information about others, such as when you exchange emails with people who don’t use our products or if you choose to give our products access to your contacts so our editing products make appropriate spelling suggestions. We use the contact information and other information we receive about non-users through user content only to provide our products to you and will not use it to contact, advertise, or market to such individuals. 

Information from other sources. We may collect information about users and non-users that’s publicly available, and we may license data such as your contact info or information about your company or job function from third parties. In addition, we may receive information about you from third parties that you choose to connect with through our online marketplace. For example, if you integrate a third-party marketplace product with a Superhuman account(s), we may receive metrics related to your use of that product or other content depending upon your settings with the third party. This data may be combined with the other information we collect and might include aggregate-level data, such as which IP addresses correspond to zip codes or countries.

Information we infer. Finally, we may infer information about you based on the information we collect. For example, we may make inferences about your approximate location based on your IP address, predict that you are interested in certain products we offer based on your usage data and past purchases, and, depending upon your account settings, we may infer what industry you work in and your writing style based on your use of our products.

How We Use Information We Collect
---------------------------------

How we use the information we collect depends upon how you use our products and your privacy settings. We use information to:

*   Provide and tailor our products to you. We use the information we collect to provide our products to you and to power rich, interactive, and personalized experiences while using them. For example, we process your user content and usage data to show you context-appropriate and personalized suggestions for writing, communications, and scheduling, to prioritize your workflows, and to offer tips on optimizing your use of our products.
    
*   Improve our products and build new ones. We’re continually developing new ways of making our products smarter, faster, more secure, and more helpful, and imagining new products we could build. For example, we analyze usage data to help us decide what new features to build or improve.
    
*   Develop and improve AI. We also use information we collect to train our AI models. You can decide whether Superhuman can use your user content to train our AI models by adjusting the available training control(s) in your account settings.
    
*   Secure our products and troubleshoot problems. We use the information we collect to resolve technical issues that arise with our products. For example, technical data and usage data help us to track outages and monitor security within our products. 
    
*   Process payments. If you are a paying customer, we work with payment processors to process your payment information to enable your transaction. If you purchase our products through a third-party app store or payment processor, you may provide your payment information directly to those providers—not to us. 
    
*   Communicate with you and provide customer service. We use information we collect to communicate with you, such as to resolve issues you encounter with our products or to provide account or product notices. For example, if you contact our support team, we may need access to account information to respond to your request. 
    
*   Market and advertise our products to you. We do not use your user content for marketing or advertising purposes. Depending on your settings, we do use some of the other information we collect (such as your email address, the types of products you have purchased, your usage data, and inferences we may have made about you) to send marketing communications, advertise our products to you on third-party sites and services, and otherwise promote our products and conduct market research. See more info on our advertising practices [below](https://superhuman.com/legal/privacy-policy#sectionSingleColumn_34DjNLbmvunaBEF93Cfuoz). 
    
*   Handle compliance issues and protect against harm. We use the information we collect to comply with law, to protect our users, Superhuman, or others, and to resolve disputes. This includes, for example, responding to legal process and governmental requests, defending our or others’ legal rights, and protecting our users, Superhuman, and others, against fraud, abuse, or other illegal, malicious, or other potentially harmful activities. 

When We Disclose Information
----------------------------

We disclose information to the types of recipients and in the scenarios described below.  

*   The Superhuman family of companies. Companies within the Superhuman corporate family may access information about you, including for business operations, product integration, development, and improvement, and to support promotion of our products. 
    
*   Trusted service providers. We use trusted service providers to help power our products and operate our business. They help with things like payment processing, AI technology, and cloud storage. These trusted service providers are bound by agreements that require them to follow data privacy and security requirements and to follow our instructions. For example, we restrict our AI service providers from training their models on user content of Superhuman customers. 
    
*   Marketplace Participants. Using our online marketplace, you can choose to build, access, use, purchase, or integrate (collectively, “use”) agents, apps, packs, applications, code, plugins, content, services, extensions, or other third-party offerings with your Superhuman account(s). If you choose to use a third-party offering, Superhuman may disclose information to that third party and/or an associated API provider in accordance with your settings. Superhuman does not own or control the third-party offerings available through our marketplace, so please review the policies and choices offered by any third party (including an associated API provider) you choose to engage or integrate. 
    
*   Advertising partners. We engage other companies to serve advertisements promoting our products and our company and to perform related services. We do not make user content available to these companies. These companies may use Cookies to collect limited information about your interactions with our websites, such as a cookie ID or device identifier and a link you click or page you visit on our websites. In addition, we may work with advertising partners to translate your email address or phone number into a unique identifier that such partners can then use to show ads promoting our products on other websites and online services. These activities–disclosing unique IDs and disclosing data through Cookies–may constitute “targeted advertising”, “sharing”, or “selling” under certain privacy laws, and depending on where you live, we may require your consent or you may be able to opt out of such activities. See “[Your Rights and Choices](https://superhuman.com/legal/privacy-policy#sectionSingleColumn_1oJ1lf5uPObRHb9hkmKhRa)” below for more. 
    
*   Government, legal, and similar authorities. We may disclose information about you to governmental agencies, regulators, and other authorities or authorized parties to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or appropriate governmental request. We may also disclose your personal information to protect ourselves, our users, or others from fraud, abuse, or other illegal or potentially harmful activities.
    
*   Disclosure in the event of merger, sale, or other asset transfer. If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, financing due diligence, reorganization, bankruptcy, receivership, purchase or sale of some or all assets, or transition of service to another provider, then your information may be sold or transferred as part of such a transaction, as permitted by law and/or contract.
    
*   With your consent or otherwise at your direction. If you consent to us disclosing your information to another user or other recipient or otherwise direct us to share your information, we may do so.

We may use and disclose data that has been de-identified so that it can no longer reasonably be used to identify you. We commit to maintaining and using such information in de-identified form and not to attempt to re-identify the information, except for the purpose of determining whether our de-identification processes satisfy applicable legal requirements.

Security and Retention
----------------------

We design our products with security in mind, and we use a combination of safeguards and processes designed to secure data, including encryption, secure network configuration, and other measures, including encryption, network segregation, and access minimization. 

We retain personal data for as long as necessary to provide our products to you, to complete the transactions you have requested, to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, and for other legitimate business purposes. We retain the data we collect for different periods of time depending on what it is, how it’s used, and how you configure your settings.

For example, where we process information for marketing purposes or with your consent, we process the data until you ask us to stop and for a short period after this (to allow us to implement your requests). We also keep a record of the fact that you have asked us not to send you direct marketing or to process your data so that we can respect your request in the future.

Your Rights and Choices
-----------------------

We offer you controls to manage your information and communications preferences with us. 

*   AI training control. As described [above](https://superhuman.com/legal/privacy-policy#sectionSingleColumn_34DjNLbmvunaBEF93Cfuoz), you can decide whether Superhuman can use your user content to train our AI models by adjusting the available training control(s) in your account settings.
    
*   Opt out of targeted advertising. We work with advertising partners to promote our products on other websites and online services. Depending on your location, you can opt out of these disclosures following the instructions presented when you click the link titled “Your Privacy Choices” on the footer of each Superhuman product website. 
    
*   Control cookies and similar technologies. You can use controls in your internet browser to limit how the websites you visit use cookies or withdraw your consent by clearing or blocking cookies. Depending on your location, we offer additional controls on our websites to turn off use of cookies, pixels, and similar technologies for non-essential purposes. Please see our [Privacy and Data Rights, Choices and Cookies page](https://support.grammarly.com/hc/en-us/articles/40540355410957-Superhuman-Privacy-and-Data-Rights-Choices-and-Cookies) for more information.
    
*   Unsubscribe from marketing communications. You can unsubscribe from our marketing emails by following the instructions in those emails, adjusting the marketing communications preferences in your settings, or emailing us at [privacy@superhuman.com](mailto:privacy@superhuman.com).
    
*   Mobile push notifications. With your permission, we may send push notifications to your mobile device. You can deactivate these notifications at any time by changing the settings on your mobile device.
    
*   Data rights. Depending on where you live, you may have rights under privacy laws to access, correct, or delete your personal data, as well as other rights, all as described below. Please review our [Privacy and Data Rights, Choices and Cookies page](https://support.grammarly.com/hc/en-us/articles/40540355410957-Superhuman-Privacy-and-Data-Rights-Choices-and-Cookies) for information on how to make these requests for the different Superhuman products. 

Data Transfers
--------------

We may transfer and process your data outside of the country where you live. Countries’ data protection laws vary, with some providing more protection than others. Regardless of where your information is processed, we apply the protections described in this policy and we comply with certain legal frameworks relating to the transfer of data, including ensuring that relevant safeguards are in place for the transfer of data where required by law. See more in the [Additional European Information](https://superhuman.com/legal/privacy-policy#sectionSingleColumn_11U1b02vomi138QlYdrrAr) section below.

Related Privacy Information
---------------------------

Organizational Users

If you use our products under the management of a company, organization, educational institution, or other legal entity (such as if your employer gives you access to our inbox assistant tools for work or if you open an account on behalf of an entity) (“Organization”), please note: 

*   This Privacy Policy does not apply to content you upload to or output from our products using such accounts. Instead, we process such content on behalf of and in accordance with the contract and data protection terms with that Organization. 
    
*   Your Organization can access and control your account. If you created an account using an email address belonging to your Organization, we may share your email address or other usage information with the administrators or representatives of that Organization.
    
*   If you join an Organization account or create an account with an email address belonging to your Organization, we may suggest you as a potential collaborator to other users of that account.
    
*   You should contact your Organization to exercise any of your rights related to your information. If you contact us with a request, we will refer your request to the Organization that provides you with access to the product, or ask that you do the same, and we will assist that Organization in responding to your request.

Our Online Marketplace

Third-party offerings made available to you through our online marketplace are not owned or controlled by Superhuman. Please refer to the terms, documentation, and policies offered by such third parties to understand their data and security practices.

Additional US State Law Information
-----------------------------------

Some US states have enacted privacy laws that grant their residents certain rights and require specific disclosures (“State Privacy Laws”). If you reside in California, Colorado, Connecticut, Delaware, Indiana, Iowa, Maryland, Minnesota, Montana, Nebraska, New Hampshire, New Jersey, Oregon, Rhode Island, Tennessee, Texas, Utah, or Virginia, or another state governed by a State Privacy Law, then this section applies to you. This section also serves as our California notice at collection.

Additional Disclosures

Above, we explain how we [collect](https://superhuman.com/legal/privacy-policy#sectionSingleColumn_7khWbuWxWV3z0H1aS5Qydm), [use](https://superhuman.com/legal/privacy-policy#sectionSingleColumn_34DjNLbmvunaBEF93Cfuoz), and [disclose information](https://superhuman.com/legal/privacy-policy#sectionSingleColumn_51xg7Vm1ExSJKFeIcEvV7z) about you, as well as our [targeted advertising practices](https://superhuman.com/legal/privacy-policy#sectionSingleColumn_51xg7Vm1ExSJKFeIcEvV7z). As required by certain State Privacy Laws, we use the tables below to explain this same information.

_Use, Disclosure, and Retention of Personal Information for Business Purposes_

| Category of Personal Information | Uses of Personal Information | Category of Recipients |
| --- | --- | --- |
| • Account information (which includes identifiers, such as your email address and account ID) <br><br>• Payment information (which includes commercial information, such as records of products purchased)<br><br>• Voice data (which includes recordings to create transcriptions of communications captured through our services)<br><br>• Communications with us and feedback (which includes survey responses and interactions with our customer support or sales teams)<br><br>• Technical information and usage data (which includes internet or other electronic network activity information, such as your activity on our websites and apps and device and browser information, and identifiers, such as your IP address)<br><br>• Cookie information (which includes identifiers, such as Cookie IDs)<br><br>• Professional  information (which includes your job title or industry, which we may license from others)<br><br>• Inferences (which includes predictions, such as your approximate location based on your IP address)<br><br>• User content | • Provide and tailor our products to you; <br><br>• Improve our products and build new ones;<br><br>• Develop and improve AI (subject to your settings);<br><br>• Secure our products and troubleshoot problems; <br><br>• Process payments; <br><br>• Communicate with you and provide customer service; <br><br>• Market our products to you (excluding user content); and<br><br>• Handle compliance issues and protect against harm. | • The Superhuman family of companies;<br><br>• Trusted service providers;<br><br>• Marketplace participants; <br><br>• Government, legal, and similar authorities; <br><br>• Recipients in connection with a merger, acquisition, or similar transaction; and<br><br>• Others with your consent or at your direction. |

When we process information that is considered “sensitive” under State Privacy Laws (such as when such information is included in your user content), we use such data only for the legally permitted purposes described above, in the same way we process user content generally. We similarly limit how we process account log-in information and contents of communications not sent to us, which may be considered “sensitive” under certain State Privacy Laws. We do not use or disclose such information for the purpose of inferring characteristics about you.

Above, we describe that we [collect](https://superhuman.com/legal/privacy-policy#sectionSingleColumn_7khWbuWxWV3z0H1aS5Qydm) personal information from various sources, including directly from you, automatically when you access or use our products, and from other sources, as well as the purposes and time periods for which we [retain](https://superhuman.com/legal/privacy-policy#sectionSingleColumn_2X92sV3D9onSGbQfyqVCVt) personal information. 

_Sales, Sharing, and Targeted Advertising_ To promote our products on third-party websites and services, we disclose the following categories of personal information to the following categories of recipients. These disclosures may be considered “sales”, “sharing”, or use of personal information for “targeted advertising” under State Privacy Laws.

| Category of Personal Information Disclosed | Category of Third-Party Recipient |
| --- | --- |
| • Identifiers (such as cookie IDs, IP addresses, or unique IDs generated from your email address or phone number)<br><br>• Internet or other electronic network activity information (such as links you click or pages you visit on a Superhuman marketing website)<br><br>• Commercial information (such as product purchase information)<br><br>• Inferences (such as predictions about your interest in certain products we offer based on your usage data) | • Advertising networks;<br><br>• Social networks |

We do not engage in sales, sharing, or targeted advertising using personal information about anyone we know to be under the age of 18.

Your Rights under State Privacy Laws

_Opt-Out Rights  
_You may opt out of activities that we engage in that may constitute “targeted advertising”, “sharing”, or “sales” of personal information under the State Privacy Laws. To do so:

*   To turn off our use of cookies and similar technologies for such purposes, follow the instructions presented when you click the link titled “Your Privacy Choices” on the footer of each Superhuman product website. Your opt-out choice will be linked to your browser only; therefore, you will need to renew your opt-out choice if you visit from a new device or browser, or if you clear your browser’s cookies. Alternatively, you may visit Superhuman websites with a Global Privacy Control or other legally recognized universal opt-out signal enabled. 
    
*   To turn off our use of unique identifiers generated from your email address or phone number for such purposes.
    
*   Please review our [Privacy and Data Rights, Choices and Cookies page](https://support.grammarly.com/hc/en-us/articles/40540355410957-Superhuman-Privacy-and-Data-Rights-Choices-and-Cookies) for more information.

_Access, Correction, and Deletion  
_You have the right to (1) request to know more about and access your personal information, including in a portable format, (2) request deletion of your personal information, and (3) request correction of inaccurate personal information. We may ask for additional information from you to verify that you are authorized to make a data rights request. Please review our [Privacy and Data Rights, Choices and Cookies page](https://support.grammarly.com/hc/en-us/articles/40540355410957-Superhuman-Privacy-and-Data-Rights-Choices-and-Cookies) for information on how to make these requests for the different Superhuman products. 

_Nondiscrimination  
_You have the right not to be discriminated against for exercising any of your privacy rights.

_Appeals  
_If we deny your request, you may appeal our decision by submitting a support ticket. If you have concerns about the result of an appeal, you may contact the attorney general in the state where you reside.

_Authorized Agents_ If you are an authorized agent seeking to make a request to opt out of sales, sharing, or targeted advertising on behalf of a consumer, please see our [Privacy and Data Rights, Choices and Cookies page](https://support.grammarly.com/hc/en-us/articles/40540355410957-Superhuman-Privacy-and-Data-Rights-Choices-and-Cookies), or you can email us at privacy@superhuman.com.  

If you reside in California, you may also designate an authorized agent to submit an access, deletion, or correction request on your behalf. We may ask authorized agents to submit proof of their authority to make a request, such as a valid power of attorney or proof that they have signed permission from the consumer who is the subject of the request. In some cases, we may contact the consumer who is the subject of the request to verify their own identity or confirm that the authorized agent has permission to submit the request. If you are an authorized agent seeking to make an access, correction, or deletion request on behalf of a California consumer, see our [Privacy and Data Rights, Choices and Cookies page](https://support.grammarly.com/hc/en-us/articles/40540355410957-Superhuman-Privacy-and-Data-Rights-Choices-and-Cookies), or you can email us at [privacy@superhuman.com](mailto:privacy@superhuman.com).  

Additional European Information
-------------------------------

This section provides additional information where you are in a country in the European Union, European Economic Area, UK or Switzerland. 

Data Controller  
Unless otherwise stated (for instance in a product-specific policy), the data controller for your information is Superhuman Platform Inc., and our contact details are as follows:

*   Superhuman Platform Inc., 2261 Market Street, STE 85232, San Francisco, CA 94114 
    
*   You can contact us at [privacy@superhuman.com](mailto:privacy@superhuman.com).

Legal Bases of Processing  
The table below outlines the legal basis and, where applicable, the legitimate interest pursued, for each purpose for which we process your information.

| Purpose | Relevant Data | Legal Basis |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Provide and tailor our products to you | All categories of data | If there’s a contractual obligation for us to process your information to fulfill our contract with you, or to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract with you: contractual necessity (Art. 6 (1)(b) GDPR/UK GDPR)<br><br>Otherwise, we process your information because we have a legitimate interest in providing a relevant, well-functioning service to you (Art.6(1)(f) GDPR/ UK GDPR) |
| Improve our products and build new ones | Account information<br><br>Voice data<br><br>Technical information<br><br>Usage data<br><br>User content<br><br>Information we infer | We have a legitimate interest in operating and improving our services and developing new products (Art. 6 (1)(f) GDPR/ UK GDPR) |
| Managing events | Account information | We have a legitimate interest in organizing and managing events (Art. 6 (1)(f) GDPR/ UK GDPR) |
| To develop and improve AI | All categories of data | We have a legitimate interest in operating and improving our services and developing new products through the use of AI (Art. 6 (1)(f) GDPR/ UK GDPR) |
| Secure our products and troubleshoot problems | Technical information<br><br>Usage data<br><br>Account information<br><br>Feedback and communications<br><br>Cookie data<br><br>Payment information | We have a legitimate interest in ensuring the security of our services and data (Art. 6 (1)(f) GDPR/ UK GDPR) |
| Process payments | Payment information | It is necessary for us to process your personal data in order to perform our contract with you, or to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract with you (Art. 6 (1)(b) GDPR/  UK GDPR)<br><br>We have a legitimate interest in improving and troubleshooting our payment processes (Art. 6 (1)(f) GDPR/ UK GDPR) |
| Communicate with you and provide customer service | Account information<br><br>Communications with us and feedback | We have a legitimate interest in managing our relationship with you (Art. 6 (1)(f) GDPR/ UK GDPR) |
| Market and advertise our products to you | Account information<br><br>Usage data<br><br>Information we infer<br><br>Cookie data | Your consent where required (Art. 6 (1)(a) GDPR/ UK GDPR)<br><br>We have a legitimate interest in promoting our products and conducting market research (Art. 6 (1)(f) GDPR/ UK GDPR) |
| Handle compliance issues and protect against harm | All categories of data | Where we have a legal obligation under EEA/UK laws (for EEA/ UK users respectively): We have a legal obligation to comply with applicable laws and regulations (Art. 6 (1)(c) GDPR/ UK GDPR)<br><br>Where we have a legal obligation under other laws: We have a legitimate interest in protecting our business interests and legal rights, and the interests and legal rights of our users (Art. 6 (1)(f) GDPR. UK GDPR) |

Your European Privacy Rights
----------------------------

If you live in a country in the European Union or the European Economic Area or live in the UK or Switzerland, you have the following rights:

*   The right of access, which enables you to receive a copy of your information. 
    
*   The right to rectification, which enables you to correct any inaccurate or incomplete information we hold about you.
    
*   The right to erasure, which enables you to ask us to delete your information in certain circumstances.
    
*   The right to restrict processing, which enables you to ask us to halt the processing of your information in certain circumstances.
    
*   The right to object, which enables you to object to us processing your information on the basis of our legitimate interests (or those of a third party), including processing for direct marketing purposes or profiling for purposes of direct marketing.
    
*   The right to data portability, which enables you to ask us to transmit information that you have provided to us, to a third party without hindrance, or to give you a copy of it so that you can transmit it to a third party, where technically feasible.
    
*   If you live in France: the right to instruct us on use of your information after your death, which enables you to instruct us now on the retention, deletion, and disclosure of your information after your death. You can change or revoke such instructions at any time.
    
*   If you live in Italy: the right to stop your heirs exercising your GDPR rights after your death through a written declaration. You may change or revoke these instructions at any time. This does not affect the exercise, by third parties, of property rights arising from your death, nor the right to defend their interests in court.

These rights may be limited, for example, if fulfilling your request would reveal personal data about another person, or if you ask us to delete information which we are required by law or have compelling legitimate interests to keep. 

If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please review our [Privacy and Data Rights, Choices and Cookies page](https://support.grammarly.com/hc/en-us/articles/40540355410957-Superhuman-Privacy-and-Data-Rights-Choices-and-Cookies).

Wherever we rely on your consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal. We may however have other legal grounds for processing your data for other purposes, such as those set out above. 

If you have unresolved concerns, you can contact us at privacy@superhuman.com. You also have the right to complain to a data protection authority in the country that you reside in, the country of your place of work, or the country where the alleged infringement took place. If you are based in the EEA, details of EEA data protection authorities are available [here](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/about-edpb/members_en). In the UK, this is the Information Commissioner’s Office and their website is [here](https://ico.org.uk/make-a-complaint/). In Switzerland, the contact details are available [here](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/en/contact-2). 

Data transfers

_Transfers to the United States  
_For personal data about EEA, Swiss and UK individuals, we comply with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework, the UK Extension of the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework, each as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce (collectively, the “Frameworks”), regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data transferred from the EEA, UK, and Switzerland in reliance on the Frameworks. 

As described in Superhuman Platform Inc.’s Frameworks certification, we have certified that we adhere to the Frameworks Principles with respect to such information. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework program and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/).

In compliance with the Frameworks, we commit to resolve complaints about our processing of your personal data under the Frameworks. If you have questions about our compliance with Frameworks Principles, you should first contact us at: [privacy@superhuman.com](mailto:privacy@superhuman.com). 

Under the Frameworks, we commit to refer unresolved complaints concerning our handling of personal data received under the Frameworks to VeraSafe, an alternative dispute resolution provider based in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please visit [here](https://verasafe.com/public-resources/dispute-resolution/submit-dispute/) for more information or to file a complaint.

If your complaint is not resolved through these channels, under certain conditions, a binding arbitration option may be available before a Data Privacy Framework Panel. For additional information, please visit: [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/framework-article/ANNEX-I-introduction](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/framework-article/ANNEX-I-introduction). 

Finally, we remain responsible under the Onward Transfer Principle for personal data that we disclose to third parties for processing on our behalf. To learn more about the Frameworks or to view our certification, please visit the Frameworks [website](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/). The Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over our compliance with the Frameworks.

_Transfers to other third countries_ For transfers from the EEA/UK to other countries, we rely on standard contractual clauses published by the EU Commission or the UK government or recognized in Switzerland.

You can ask us for a copy of the relevant contracts or other measures we rely upon to transfer personal data by using the contact details below.

Contact Information
-------------------

You can contact us with questions relating to this Privacy Policy by emailing us at [privacy@superhuman.com](mailto:privacy@superhuman.com).

We’ve appointed VeraSafe as our representative in the EEA and UK for data protection matters. You can contact VeraSafe in matters related to personal information processing using [this contact form](https://www.verasafe.com/privacy-services/contact-article-27-representative). Alternatively: 

*   For users in the EEA: You can contact VeraSafe at VeraSafe Ireland Ltd, Unit 3D North Point House, North Point Business Park, New Mallow Road, Cork T23AT2P, Ireland.
    
*   For users in the UK: You can contact VeraSafe at VeraSafe United Kingdom Ltd., 37 Albert Embankment, London SE1 7TL, United Kingdom.

Superhuman Platform, Inc. has appointed Bird & Bird DPO Services SRL as its Data Protection Officer (DPO). The DPO can be contacted at: Email: [dpo.superhuman@twobirds.com](mailto:dpo.superhuman@twobirds.com); Post: Bird & Bird DPO Services SRL, Avenue Louise 235 b 1, 1050 Brussels, Belgium.
